WONSUK CHA

Automation & iOS Developer

INFO

ADDRESS

#204, Soojeong-villa, 834-53 Yeoksam-dong, Gangnam-gu, Seoul, Korea

PHONE

+82-10-6298-8611

EMAIL

wonscha@outlook.com

SKILL

AUTOMATION DEV

UIPath

Automation Anywhere VBA



MOBILE APP DEV

Swift

Javascript React Native



WEB DEV

HTML CSS

Javascript



PROFILE

Passionate and self-motivated Automation and iOS Developer with more than three years of intensive development experience. As a fast-learner and a challenger, played an active part in a variety of industries and currently running a business specialized in iOS development.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

CEO, Cha & Company; Seoul, S.Korea

Jan 2020 - Present

- Identified new customers and managed relationship with customers.
- Planned and developed iOS applications such as Moon Phase Calendar App and Offline Cafe Music App for iOS market which are expected to release in July 2020.

Senior Automation Developer, Daimler Truck Asia; Tokyo, Japan Jan 2019 - Dec 2019

- Designed automated business process and developed automation bots reflecting the optimization and scalability.
- Successfully automated 9 vehicle design processes in R&D function handling 20,000 hours of work per year.

Automation Consultant & Developer, Deloitte Consulting; Tokyo, Japan Oct 2016 - Nov 2018

- Served as the main liaison between the team and the client responsible for the client relationship management.
- Designed To-Be model after implementation of RPA and OCR solutions.
- Developed more than 30 bots to run 3 automated processes handling 200,000 hours of work per year.

LANGUAGE

English •••••

Korean

Japanese

•••••

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science, Seoul National University; Seoul, S.Korea Feb 2014

- Cumulative GPA: 3.66 / 4.3 (Honors: Cum Laude)

Dongsan Christian High School; Gyeonggi-do, S.Korea Feb 2005